is potentially a problem in the future for Republicans.
If a Democratic president someday calls the National Guard
to a red state over what they see as open rebellion,
but is what amounts to a demonstration that gets rowdy.
I mean, is that not a fear here?
They're posting pictures of their kids
because it's a demonstration.
They have a sniper on top of a building
firing a high caliber rifle at a nice facility
because it's a demonstration
and they are engaging a vehicle ramming attack.
But the National Guard isn't being sent to Texas.
The National Guard isn't being sent to Dallas
where that sniper was.
Because the Dallas Police Department
and the governor of Texas,
well, you walked right into that one,
have responded to every call for assistance and help.
They gave a stand down order in Chicago
and they gave a stand down order in Portland.
Do you realize that there's 11,000
federal law enforcement officers in Oregon?
That's larger than the size of the FBI.
Local and state police are resourced
to deal with this kind of riotous assembly,
but they have refused.
They've been given a stand down order.
They've arrested some 70 people since June.
They've been arresting folks on the ground.
They refuse what you're saying outright.